欢迎回来。
Welcome back.
所以我们开始配置我们的 VS 代码编辑器
So we started configuring our VS code editor
在课程的一开始，但现在，
in the very beginning of the course, but now at this point,
我们准备安装三个额外的扩展
we are ready to install three additional extensions
这将使我们的生活更轻松
that will make our lives a little bit easier
当我们编写 HTML 和 CSS 代码时。
as we code HTML and CSS.
因此，让我们在这里转到我们的扩展面板。
And so let's head over to our extensions panel here.
我想在这里安装的第一个扩展
And the first extension that I want to install here
被称为，图像
is called, Image
预览。
preview.
所以就是这个，我已经安装了它。
So it's this one and I already have it installed.
所以我只需要点击启用。
So I just need to click on enable.
好的。
Okay.
所以这是第一个。
So that's the first one.
而这个要做的是在我们的 HTML 中，
And what this one is going to do is that here in our HTML,
它现在在这个装订线中显示这个小图像预览
it now displays this small image preview here in this gutter
因为它被称为。
as it's called.
所以这里我们有这个
So here we have this one
然后这里的这张图片也在这里
and then this image here is also right here
我们在哪里声明它。
where we declare it.
所以我们将它包含在我们的代码中，
So where we include it in our code,
这有时会非常有帮助。
and this can be extremely helpful sometimes.
所以这就是为什么我真的想给你看这个。
So that's why I really wanted to show you this one.
我想给你看的下一个叫做
The next one that I want to show you is called
颜色荧光笔
color highlighter
或突出显示。
or highlight.
所以这里就是这个
So it's this one here
再一次，我已经安装了它。
and again, I already have it installed.
我只是启用它。
I just enable it.
实际上这个，我还不能给你看
And actually this one, I cannot show you yet
它看起来像什么，因为它只与 CSS 相关。
what it looks like, because it will only be relevant in CSS.
但请相信我，这个扩展真的非常有帮助
But trust me that this extension is really, really helpful
用于在 CSS 中可视化颜色。
for visualizing colors in CSS.
接下来是一个名为自动重命名的扩展
Next up is an extension called auto rename
标签
tag
所以这个，
So this one,
你看到它又一次非常受欢迎。
and you see it's an extremely popular one, once again.
所以你必须下载它并启用它。
So you have to download it and enable it.
然后这里发生的是，
And then what happens here is that,
当我们改变一个元素的名字时，
when we changed the name of an element,
假设我们实际上想让这个成为一个 div，
let's say we actually wanted to make this one a div,
然后你会看到它自动也改变了关闭一个。
then you see it automatically also changes the closing one.
所以结束标签。
So the closing tag.
好的。
Okay.
这又非常有帮助
And this again is extremely helpful
它使我们编写 HTML 的生活更轻松，
it makes our life writing HTML a bit easier,
因为相信我，我们需要一直这样做，
because trust me, we need to do this all the time,
就像更改元素名称一样。
like changing the element name.
好的。
Okay.
现在我们需要做的另一件事，
Now another thing that we need to do,
或者至少如果我们愿意，我们可以做到，
or at least that we can do if we want,
就是回到我们的设置然后转回来
is to go back to our settings and then turn back
在我们停用的这个设置上
on this setting that we deactivated
在本节的开头。
at the beginning of the section.
那就是汽车，
So that's the auto,
让我们拼写正确。
let's spell that right.
所以自动关闭标签。
So auto close tag.
所以让我们重新启用它，因为我认为在这一点上
So let's enable this back because I think at this point
你不会再犯忘记的错误
you will no longer make the mistake of forgetting
结束标记。
a closing tag.
所以现在我们可以让 VS 代码为我们完成这项工作。
And so now we can allow VS code to do that work for us.
例如，如果我们想在这里写一个段落。
So for example, if we wanted to write a paragraph here.
然后现在你看到 HTML
Then now you see HTML
自动为我们关闭该元素。
automatically close that element for us.
好的。但我们不需要这个，
Okay. But this we don't need,
现在，我们要安装最重要的
and now, we are going to install the most important
也是最有用的一个，
and the most useful one of all,
这就是所谓的实时服务器。
and that is called live server.
所以这里就是这个
So it's this one here,
拥有近 1200 万次下载的实时服务器
live server with almost 12 million downloads
这个受欢迎是有原因的。
and this one is popular for a reason.
所以，我只是c在这里启用
So, I just click enable here
和，
and,
所以当我现在去我的 HTML
so when I go now to my HTML
让我们关闭这个。
and let's close this one down.
所以关闭侧边栏。
So close down the sidebar.
现在在这个酒吧里，我们应该有
Now down here in this bar, we should have
现在这个上线按钮。
now this go live button.
好的。
Okay.
所以希望在安装这个实时服务器扩展之后，
So hopefully after installing this live server extension,
你也可以在这里看到这个按钮
you can also see this button down here
在这个状态栏中。
in this status bar.
所以当我现在点击这个，然后它开始
So when I now click this, then it starting
我们得到这个服务器启动的消息
and we get this message that server is started at
这个端口号在这里。
this port number here.
让我们关闭它。
Let's close that.
你看，它打开了一个新标签，
And you see it, that it opened a new tab,
其中包含我们的页面，对吗？
which contains our page, right?
所以基本上看起来完全一样，
So basically it looks exactly the same,
但有一个很大的区别。
but there is one very big difference.
所以，
So,
让我们，
let's,
假设我们想在这里改变它。
let's say we wanted to change this here.
我将称之为 JONAS 代码。
I'm going to call it JONAS CODE.
现在，当我保存这个文件时，仔细看看这里发生了什么。
And now, look closely what happens here as I save this file.
所以我现在点击命令 S，或者在 Windows 上控制 S。
So I hit command S now, or control S on windows.
你看看发生了什么。
And you see what happened.
它自动重新加载页面
It automatically reloaded the page
无需我们做任何事情。
without us having to do anything.
所以我们所做的只是保存到代码中
So all we did was save to code
然后会发生的是这个页面在这里
and what will then happen is that this page here
自动更新。
gets automatically updated.
所以我们在这里所做的所有改变
So all the changes that we did here
基本上会被注入这个页面。
will basically get injected into this page.
和，
And,
现在，我们可以看到反射
now, we can then see the reflection
我们的变化立即。
of our changes immediately.
所以我现在放回去了。
So I put it back now.
我再次点击，命令或控制 S 来保存它
I hit again, command or control S to save it
你会立即看到它恢复到以前的样子。
and immediately you see it going back to what it was before.
现在如果我们想停止这种连接，
Now if we wanted to stop this connection,
一旦我们完成开发，
once we are done developing,
我们所要做的就是点击这里
all we have to do is to click down here
在此图标上，它显示端口 5500。
on this icon here where it says port 5500.
顺便说一句，这个端口号正是我们所拥有的
And by the way, this port number is exactly what we have
这里。
here.
好的。
Okay.
所以只是为了好奇，
So just for the sake of curiosity,
这里的这个意味着它是一个本地主机服务器。
this one here means that it's a local host server.
所以基本上就像你现在有一个网络服务器
So basically it's like you have now a web server
在自己的电脑上运行。
on your own computer running.
然后我们实际上运行了这段代码
And then we have actually this code running
在这个端口号。
at this port number.
所以这个港口，
And so this port,
它基本上就像您的网络服务器的子地址。
it's basically like a sub address of your web server.
所以本地本地主机服务器，
So of the local local host server,
但这并不重要。
but this doesn't really matter.
重要的是这现在有效
What matters is that this now works
它真的非常有帮助
and it is really, really helpful
对于我们的开发工作流程。
for our development workflow.
现在，如果由于某种原因你无法完成这项工作
Now, if for some reason you could not make this work
在您的计算机上，那么当然不用担心。
on your computer, then of course don't worry.
所以你仍然可以用旧的方式来做。
So you can still do it the old way.
所以基本上我们一直在做的方式，
So basically the way we have been doing it all along,
直到这一点。
up until this point.
所以你可以从你的文件系统中打开文件
So you can just open up the file from your file system
像我们一样，然后继续手动刷新它。
like we did, and then keep refreshing it manually.
对。但是我们，现在，这里不再需要这个标签
Right. But we, right now, no longer need this tab here
因为我们现在有了实时连接。
because we now have our live connection.
所以我们有我们的实时服务器来服务这个页面
So we have our live server serving up this page
每当我们进行一些编辑时。
whenever we do some edits.
好的。有了这个
All right. And with that
我们现在准备应对
we are now ready to tackle
或最后少两个编码挑战
or final less two coding challenges
在这个 HTML 基础部分。
in this HTML fundamental section.